memeo.com 2016-05-14

# Memeo - A Division of UNICOM Global :: Privacy

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how Memeo Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web sites: www.memeo.com, me.memeo.com, share.memeo.com, memeosend.com, memeoconnect.com or c1.memeo.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Memeo through one of the following:

Email: [privacy@memeo-inc.com](mailto:privacy@memeo-inc.com)

Postal: Memeo Inc. Attn: Privacy  
469 El Camino Real, Suite 201   
Santa Clara, CA 95050  
USA

Telephone: +1.408.834.7168

## Collection and Use of Personal Information

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

We may use this information to:

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess the needs of your business to determine suitable products
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Display content based upon your interests

**Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us a t[unsubscribe@memeo-inc.com.](mailto:unsubscribe@memeo-inc.com)

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others. Please note that we cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information.

**Information Obtained from Third Parties**

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.

## Information Sharing

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * if Memeo Inc, is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so

## Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We may use cookies, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

We use another company to place cookies on your computer to collect non-personally identifiable information to compile aggregated statistics for us about visitors to our site.

**Web beacons**

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used and may be used in some of our emails to let us know which emails and links have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns.

**Links to Other Web Sites**

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Memeo Inc. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

**Co-branded sites**

Some pages may have the look and feel of being on [www.memeo.com](http://www.memeo.com/), however the information collected on these pages may not be covered under our privacy statement. All information collected on [www.parature.com](http://www.parature.com/) (support.memeo.com) is owned and controlled by that companies privacy statement.

Our privacy statement does not apply to the information collected on these co-branded sites. For further detail, you should read the privacy statement of our co-branded partner.

## Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [security@memeo-inc.com.](mailto:security@memeo-inc.com)

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

## Additional Policy Information

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

**Customer Testimonials / Comments / Reviews**

We post customer testimonials/comments/reviews on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial.

**Correcting, Deleting and Updating Your Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [privacy@memeo-inc.com](mailto:privacy@memeo-inc.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## Contact Information

You can contact us by writing or email us at the address below:

Memeo Inc. Attn: Privacy  
469 El Camino Real, Suite 201   
Santa Clara, CA 95050  
USA

Email: [privacy@memeo-inc.com](mailto:privacy@memeo-inc.com)

**Privacy policy for downloaded software applications**

This section of the policy covers how Memeo treats personal information that Memeo collects and receives from our downloaded software applications. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Memeo does not own or control, or to people that Memeo does not employ or manage.

The following section explains Memeo's information practices, including information it collects from you, how Memeo will use the information, and the choices you have with your information. By installing and using the Memeo Software, you consent to these information practices. When you purchase or license products from Memeo, Memeo may collect registration-related information, such as name, home or work addresses, email addresses, telephone numbers, etc.), information about your responses to Memeo's offerings, transaction-related information (such as payment methods, billing information and product purchases) and customer service related information.

Memeo will use this information to improve its products, to improve your experience and use of Memeo's products, to fulfill your orders, to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries, and to offer you other products, programs or services that may be of interest to you. The information will not be shared with third parties unless specifically authorized by you or in response to a legal process. Each time you receive any promotions by e-mail from Memeo, you will be given the opportunity in that e-mail to unsubscribe from any further promotions. Keep in mind, however, that you understand and agree that Memeo may continue to contact you about important information concerning your transactions with Memeo, or to provide you with important notices about your Memeo Software.

Memeo may automatically check your version of the Memeo Software. Memeo may automatically update the Memeo Software on your hardware system to improve the performance and capabilities of the Memeo Software. Memeo will assign a unique identifying number to the Memeo Software installed on your hardware device. This unique number will not be identified with any of your personal information. Memeo may also query your computer on an anonymous basis to determine if the Memeo Software is running on your system. Memeo will use this anonymous information to improve the Memeo Software and its offerings to you. You will be given the option to send configuration data and crash reports concerning your use of Memeo Software; you also will be given the option to provide your e-mail address with this information so that Memeo may get in touch with you. Memeo maintains the confidential information you provide in a secure database. Please keep in mind that while Memeo has established safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of you information, it cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with the information practices disclosed in this section (for example, in the event of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate applicable law or policies).

If you have questions or suggestions, please e-mail us at [privacy@memeo-inc.com](mailto:privacy@memeo-inc.com)
